SINA OLFATI

Full Stack Developer

🔀 sinaolfati6@gmail.com 📞 +989941669736 😲 Kermanshah, Iran 🛗 26/01/2003

https://sina-olfati.github.io/sina-olfati-site in https://www.linkedin.com/in/sina-olfati-872950233

https://github.com/sina-olfati

Profile

I'm a 20 years old passionate developer (React.Js + Next.Js + Node.Js). I've invested my youth hours in deep learning to optimize myself to add the most value to your company; Doubt that? Just visit my site, ask my former employers... Or hire me and watch my career for 1 month.

Leave anything you worry about to me; improving your site creatively? Leading a team? Making your work environment more friendly? What are you waiting for?

Skills			
React.js	• • • • •	Next.js	• • • • •
Node.Js	• • • • •	MongoDB	• • • • •
TypeScript	• • • • •	PWA	• • • • •
i18next	• • • • •	Redux	• • • • •
Redux-Thunk	• • • • •	Recoil	• • • • •
Rest API	• • • • •	SPA	• • • • •
Axios	• • • • •	Material UI	• • • • •
Tailwind	• • • • •	Bootstrap	• • • • •
Responsive Design	• • • •	Docker	• • • • •
Git/GitHub	• • • • •	Scrum	• • • • •
JavaScript	• • • • •	CSS	• • • • •
HTML	• • • •		

Experience

08/2022 – 11/2022 London, England(UK)

JavaScript Developer

VModel ☑

- Led the web development team, consisting of 4 members, for 3 weeks; Increased quality and speed by 50%
- Helped the members with coding when they were stuck; Increased speed and teamwork spirit by 40%-60%
- Made unique pages by building user-friendly, interactive and innovative user interfaces; 60% improvement in user experience

Contact: Shinor Spellz - WhatsApp number: +447377919954

05/2022 – 08/2022 Tehran, Iran

Front-end Developer (React.js) Intern

Clickhub (Noavaran Dadepardaz click)

- Learned and applied useful front-end skills; being able to build sites 200% more professionally
- Learned: Redux Redux-Thunk, TypeScript, PWA, Material UI, Formik, Docker, Scrum, PSD to HTML & CSS

Contact: Nima Bakhshi - WhatsApp & Telegram Number: +989363806000

Languages

EnglishPersian (Farsi)Kurdish"Perfect" grade diplomaNativeNative

Portfolio

Sina's Site 7

• Technologies: React.js, TypeScript, PWA (It is installable), Material Ui, SPA, Formik, i18next (made it multilingual), JavaScript, CSS, HTML

Sina's Shop 🛮

• Technologies: React, Redux, Redux-Thunk, TypeScript, PWA, SPA, JavaScript, CSS, HTML

Education

08/2021 – present Bachelor's of Teaching Science
Tabriz, Iran Allameh Amini University ☑

2018 "'Perfect'' grade English language diploma
Qasr-e Shirin, Iran Padideh Academy of Foreign Languages

2016 Honorary diploma in mathematics

Kangaroo International Olympiad ☑